http://www.eyeglass.com/pages/our-privacy-policy

Styles LennonVintageHard to FindRetroFiftiesClubmasterMen Frames By ShapeBy Material
Contact Us
Pupillary Distance (PD)
Terms And Conditions
We collect personal data from you when you register on our site, order eyeglasses, subscribe to our newsletter, visit our website, respond to a survey or fill out a form. Your personal data means any information relating to you, in particular your name and contact details such as your home address, your telephone number or your email address.
Please take the time to read this Privacy Notice carefully, it is very important that you fully understand how we are processing your personal data and how we are protecting your privacy. If you have any question regarding our use of your personal data, you can of course contact us.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you access our website, we automatically collect and store some of your data in our server logs and in cookies to enhance your customer experience.
How Do We Use Your Information?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
To improve our website
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To improve customer service
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To process transactions
We may share your billing information with the external payment service providers we partner with, but only as is necessary for the processing of your payment or to prevent or detect fraud. These companies have agreed not to retain, share, store or use your Personally Identifiable Information which we pass to them for any secondary purposes.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
In some cases, these may require interfacing with third party solutions and software.
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. We do not store credit card information ever!
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do We Use Cookies?
Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.
Do We Disclose Any Information To Outside Parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties you're personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Some of your information may be used by any eyeglass.com affiliates to contact you about sales, new products, special offers, and new site features, unless you have opted to not receive promotional communications. Each email sent to you by our affiliates and / or other companies within our group will include an 'unsubscribe' link.
Florida Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the Florida Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the Florida Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the "My Account" section of the site and making the necessary changes themselves.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 16 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 16 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes To Our Privacy Policy
We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Notice, in particular to make it compliant with new laws and regulations regarding data protection. This Privacy Notice may change from time to time, but we will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Notice without your explicit consent.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
